[Music]
In the not too distant future, next Sunday, A.D.
There was a guy named Joel, not too different from you or me.
He worked at Gizmonic Institute, just another face in a red gel suit.
He did a good job cleaning up the place, but his boss didn't like him so they shot him into space.
[Music]
We'll send the cheesy movies the worst we can find.
He'll have to sit and watch them all and the monitor is mine.
Now keep in mind Joel can't control where the movies begin or end.
Because he used those special parts to make his robot friends.
[Music]
Robot, robot called Camo, Chipsy, Tom Servo, Crow.
If you're wondering how he eats and breathes and other science facts,
Then repeat to yourself, it's just the show.
I should really just relax for Mystery Science Theater 3000.
[Music]
And next up in the comedy competition, W.J. Wiedelhofer and Peanut.
Hi everybody, actually I'm Joel Robinson on the satellite a lot,
but I was just thinking that if I ever get down to earth,
one thing I want to do is go on Star Search and go toe to toe with ten time comedy winner, Geechee Guy.
But the only way I can win is by doing some ventriloquism.
So I'd like to introduce you to my robot.
He's a woozle and his name is Peanut.
Now say hi to the nice audience, Peanut.
Hello to the nice audience, Peanut.
Oh come on, quit your clowning.
Hey, come on, can't you see any, look at the nice audience, how well mannered and nicely dressed they are.
I want to go out and get me some chicks.
Come on, I have a whore you, please don't do that.
Cut your clowning.
Commercial sign in fifteen seconds.
Can't you say anything friendly to the audience, to this nice audience?
Yeah, it certainly is nice to get out of that stinky suitcase.
Oh come on, Joel, I can't go through with this, it's ridiculous.
I feel like Waylon Flowers in Madam.
Come on, you promised.
Commercial sign in five seconds.
Judge Paloma Picasso gives you a one.
From Michael J. Pollard, a one.
Gilderoy gives you a one.
And from John Sebastian, a four.
Overall score, one point seven five.
Commercial sign now.
And we'll be right back.
If we would have stuck with it, we could have won.
Yeah, well you try sitting still through that.
Well maybe next time I will.
Yeah, and that's pretty good, isn't it?
And she's giving it back to you.
Yeah, I'm giving it back to you.
Perfect fail.
Hello, this is my little buddy, T.J. Stinky Muffin.
But I call him Stinky. Say hello to the folks, Stinky.
Hello, folks.
That's good.
Why don't you tell the people what you did today, Stinky?
Oh, can it, Sporky, get me a beer.
That's it, that's it. Party's over. Forget it, forget it.
You can dish it out, but you can't take it.
And next up, the juvenile dance competition.
I gotta get me a good seat for that one.
The Eisner twins are calling.
You just watch it, T.J. Cinnamon.
We're not running a ventriloquist camp around here.
That's telling them, you putridness.
Just tell them about the invention exchange, Frank.
Well, say, aren't we gonna do a short scene for Mannequin first, your wretchedness?
No, we are not going to do a short...
What is with the names, Frank?
It's Dr. Forrester, just Dr. Forrester.
I'm just trying to spice up our sagging relationship, oh, vile one.
Could we talk about this later, Frank?
Sure, your stinkiness.
My invention exchange this week, Joel,
are these easy-to-make, ready-to-wear Halloween costumes.
Just take a piece of stiffened rope, slip it around your neck, and voila, dead guys.
It's perfect for your next necktie party.
What do you think, H.R. Finklehoffer?
Joel, Joel, come on, Joel, what's wrong, buddy? Joel, Joel, come on, come on.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry. Hi, everybody. This is my invention exchange this week.
It's for people who like listening to the sounds of the ocean.
You know, sometimes you can get sick of tapes.
And this is a portable way you can hear the ocean wherever you go.
What it's got is padded headphones and a line that goes down to this conch shell.
I call it the Sony Seaman.
Neat, and you know, if you get tired of the sea, you can plug in Handel's water music.
Yeah, or play the old soundtrack from Baywatch episodes.
Or Surfside 6.
Yeah, yeah.
What do you think, sirs?
Well, I think it's almost as lame as ours, skin puppy.
Now, Joel, your experiment this week is a film which is probably Roger Corman's finest to date.
It's a film called It Conquered the World, and it's really, really, really quite bad.
But first, we're going to start you off with a light cover drum through hell
with a little something called Snow Thrills.
Send them the movie, Frank.
I'll do it when I get to it.
What, are your arms broken or something?
I'll push the button.
Oh no, Frank's dead, Joel's ozone, and we've got movie time.
Joel, come on, come on.
Let's go, we've got movie time.
I just thought it would be funny to have a shell walk there.
It was cute.
It's part of me and Dustin's sliders there.
Hal Roach presents an art gang comedy.
It's the parade of shame and wasted lives.
I did it for the kicks, man.
Snow Thrills everywhere.
Alright, Hard Castle and McCormick. It's a great show.
It's a brand new show.
Ice skaters, young and old, die from flashing blades.
You know where I come from there, rust, flashing blades.
It's true.
I thought he was fictional.
We're up in Newburgh, New York, watching hot competition on a very cold day.
Get out of the way, old man.
Hot, hot, hot.
You know, there's nothing quite as pretty on a summer day as arterial spray on the white snow.
It's too late, it's really sweet.
It's not that bad.
Get it, get it.
Show amazing speed on skates. Watch them hit it up.
We don't approve of fast girls, do we?
Hit it up?
Watch this. The crows come down to pluck the bones of the fallen skaters.
Better luck next time, Mr. Crow.
Way to go, kid.
Sprite, please.
There's a monger, run!
New York.
New York, the younger generation speed around the frozen lake and how they do go.
Hey, look, I can see Ryan O'Neill and Nolly McGraw over there.
I thought they said the younger generation.
Love means never having to watch this movie.
Skates flash in the sun as this sport gives keen enjoyment to fans of all ages.
Yes, even people with one foot in the grave like it.
Meanwhile, in the stuffed shirt competition.
Oh, oh, triplen.
And these guys really go.
Yes, it's prostitutes on ice.
Oh, oh, well, in a nice way.
Beauty, grace and rhythm.
You won't find them here.
Let's find out what these lovelies had for lunch.
Mom, get off the ice, Dad. Would you make her get off the ice?
Look at her.
Mother, get off the ice.
Here Gertrude Stein shows her moves.
A modern whirling dervish on steel and ice.
Neat.
You mean she's going to skate till she dies?
Yep.
This film is just an exercise in adjectives.
Winter winds fill bulging sails to flash speedy...
Fourth of July in Minnesota.
The sails galore in this winter's port...
Are darn hard to come by.
Fast work and speedy too.
With a cold wind blowing the sturdy craft over the frozen water.
People can be thrown as far as 50 feet from the craft and it's fun.
Yachting in winter without hot coffee in the cabin.
Nothing like losing a few toes and fingers to frostbite.
Mush mush!
I'm hungry for cream of wheat for some reason.
I'm pleased that would be nice.
(barking)
...the excitement of dog sled races over snow and ice through a fighting cliff.
Mush, mush, and the thoroughbred Siberians dash ahead.
To escape their evil tormentors.
...speed at their best, a doggone good race.
No.
What does P.J. have to say?
Isn't that John Sununu?
It's the goofy guys.
What?
...introduces the human polar bears.
They claim it great, but we have our doubts.
Get in old man, you've seen enough.
...but there's no stopping them.
They just must have their cold bath.
Some fun, eh?
Well, we'll take a hot shower if you don't mind.
Let's talk about shrinkage, shall we?
Mm-hmm.
Come on everybody, we're gonna go skiing.
We're gonna have a heck of a lot of fun.
We're gonna go die on the slopes now.
...becoming one of the most popular of winter sports is sheing.
And sheing is the correct pronunciation, they tell us.
Yeah, well, you're full of skit.
...wistles in trim for later years.
When they'll be able to glide down hills and through the valley.
Yes, it's never too early to fuse your spinal cord together.
In a few years, these children will be addicted to painkillers.
But for now, little Billy is paralyzed.
Mm.
Cross-country sheing amid schemes of winter magnificence
in Sanada's snow-severed playground.
Oh, God.
Thank you.
We're gonna take them seriously.
Woohoo!
They're coming down the mountain.
When they come.
...and the snow-covered mountains of Europe and Canada
aboard a variety of natural arenas for this sport.
Hey, come back here, Jerry. Give me my flask.
Boda bag with spiced wine.
Look, James Bond's being chased by enemy agents.
Hmm.
At the bottom, they fish through the ice for dinner.
Oh, seems some of the polar bear club didn't make it out of the hole.
Now let's watch some she-thrills.
Sheep thrills?
-She-thrills to each his own. -All worlds to each his own.
Inmates from death row are subjected to horrible experiments.
Time's over the road.
And boy, are they stupid.
The high jump is the high spot of she.
Here, balance counts.
-Watch the splatter. -Especially after you clear the chute.
There's Grandma!
Grandma!
What is she doing?
I think this was sponsored by Prudential.
See what I mean?
Look at him go!
To hell!
In a hand basket.
It's the agony of defeat auditions.
Whoa, what a fall!
It's public humiliation on a grand scale.
Collect the parts, then back to the top.
Then it's time to stand on the first aid line.
It's a dangerous sport unless you know how to land upright.
Oops, and this palooka now sells pencils on Third Avenue.
It's the biggest one-man thrill in Jack Frost's show.
I know a better one.
Forget I said that. Sorry.
Embarrassing? You bet. That guy never had a chance.
Ouch.
What? She-horring?
Now what?
I'm Sally Jussie Raphael. She-horring.
What?
They got their idea from aquaplaning.
Uh-huh.
These she-joring fans.
It's aquaplaning.
Faster they shout, so the horse again bows to the automobile.
It's a safe and fun way to blow a Saturday, or a knee.
A heap of fun.
Huh?
Uh-oh.
It's the nuttiest bobsled in town.
Oh, look.
Oh, look at them all.
Reminds you of Lemmings?
It's a death train.
I see a class action suit coming around the corner.
Watch out for that train.
Uh-oh.
Help us. We can't come back. We don't know how it works.
Oh, I can't take this. The music, that is.
It's the sled of the subgenius.
Now is the winter of our discontentment.
...speed, thrills, nerve and courage. This wins the vote.
This takes the cake.
On they dash. Faster, faster.
Pussycat, kill, kill.
Do you want to go faster?
Raise your hands if you want to go faster.
Yay!
Uh, grab the mail there, would you please?
Yeah.
Boy, all this just to get to talk to Jim McKay.
No!
Oh, shoot.
Excuse me.
Hey, what happened? Did the voiceover guy go to the bathroom or something?
Down goes Herschel Walker.
Well, we can't wait.
You'll get run over by the next sled.
The Swiss have a word for this. It's called...
I'm gonna die!
And with the greatest thrill of all, we climax Jack Frost's great show.
Snow, ice, pep, steady nerve, joy and...
Blood, flesh, entrails, the contents of a human spilled.
Thank you, Eugene Castle, for making us laugh at winter again.
And again, and again.
[Music]
Hey, my B-movie right or wrong?
I've looked at clouds from both sides now.
Ah, well, good night, everyone. That was nice. It's time for...
Oh.
Flight of the bumblebee.
Do not adjust your set. We can make it stupid.
Oh, they're giving away the ending.
Sally Frazier's on a Russ Bender and a Jonathan Hayes
'cause she drank a Tagger Casey of Dick Miller.
Hmm.
Huh?
Paul Harper, December 7th, 1941.
A date that will live in infamy.
Set of a...
Sorry, Lou, that I have to Russ off like this.
Title puns. I love 'em.
We control the executive producer.
Say, whose line is that, anyway?
Syrup by Larry Butterworth.
Hey, let's go over to Lou's place.
Lou, here. Little song, little dance, little self-dime dance.
Oh, this is great. This is really encouraging.
Mm-hmm.
You know, I'd rather watch 30-something.
Yeah, me too.
It's a TV.
Wait a minute. That's James Arneth.
Oh, that's Peter Grace.
Oh, yeah.
That's what they trade in.
Cool boat you did.
Power on.
And man is finally ready to move into space.
Next on Biography.
Oh! He changed!
I'd like to have you meet Dr. Anderson.
I assume you two gentlemen have known of each other?
Doctor, it's rare to meet so illustrious a physicist as...
Thank you, General.
Thank you. Let's cut the crap, shall we?
I'm sure you're just as distressed at my presence here as Secretary Platt.
Oh, I wouldn't say distressed.
No, certainly not, Mr. Platt.
We're all in a state of high hilarity.
We'll all wind up in a state of high mortality if you don't call off the satellite project.
Nice change-up.
Oh, but it changes if I told you. That's impossible.
Not nearly as many times as I've warned the government against such a course.
I said it when I was head of the perpetual missile program.
I said it before that when I was working on the Manhattan Project and War II.
Don't tell me you haven't read my papers on the subject.
Only your midterm.
What a remarkable career, Doctor. Every degree imaginable.
Now get out! Out!
By the way, just what are you doing at present? Retired, I understand?
I'm between gigs.
The world is full of bad heads, Mr. Platt.
So I invented diet shampoo.
I've got a great deal of respect for you, Dr. Anderson.
But this has not convinced me the satellite is a menace to the safety of the world.
What happened to the first one?
Yes, come on. Come on, come on.
What happened? What happened?
It exploded in its own orbit. Anyone know why?
Nobody? I know why. It was a warning.
I anticipated that fully three years before the satellite was launched.
You're bitter, aren't you?
You said something about the other planets wanting to keep the Earth in its place?
To keep her out of the skies.
But there's no life in the other planets.
Certainly no nightlife.
I'm not arguing theory, General.
I'm only telling you this.
Alien intelligence watches us constantly.
Of course they do.
We'll see this satellite of yours and know something must be done.
I'm here to ask you, to beg you, to save your own world.
Please.
Well, Doctor, this has become just an academic question.
In about eight seconds, the sphere will be launched during the countdown right now.
You made me go through all this for nothing? That's cold.
The elevator's broken!
I'm stuck in the wrong room!
I can see your house from here. I can see everyone's house from here.
Cyderak by Estus.
Neat. Is that the one with the parachute and the camera?
And the big payload section.
Whoa!
Hey, the house on the rock!
Claire, this pie is delicious. Did you bake it yourself?
Oh, sure.
An old family recipe my grandmother sold to the bakery.
Stop!
Tom, you want some more?
Only half a gallon or so.
Everybody's a queen.
You acting so smug about it.
You look like a man who just inherited Texas.
You might not be too far off in a sense.
Tom?
Yes, dear?
I know.
I bet you finally decided you were wrong about the satellite.
Hardly.
It's my greatest interest in life.
That and my hair.
Well, been up there for three months now and nothing horrible has happened.
Yep.
80 feet in diameter, 1,070 miles high, encircling the earth at 16,000 miles an hour.
Honey, not this again.
Can't you two talk about anything else?
I'm getting tired of hearing about nothing but satellites, isotopes, conical graduations and all the rest.
Maybe you've got something in space medicine I could use for a headache, huh?
I guess you're not getting much.
Sorry.
You have got something up your sleeve.
What about my arm?
I can't tell you, Paul.
My wife won't let me.
She thinks I'm crazy.
Well, he does eat hairballs.
The whole world thinks you're crazy.
Maybe even me.
Which results in creativity.
What's the big secret?
I like frilly things.
Tom, please.
Please.
Honey, this is too big.
But you promised.
Please.
Paul will understand.
Maybe nobody else on earth but Paul will understand.
I'll try.
Come in to the other room.
Okay, but you're never going to beat me at arm wrestling.
Don't take it so hard, Claire.
See what you've got.
Come on, I'll wash and you wipe.
That's it.
Where does one buy the kit?
It'll be just a second.
It's a koroki machine.
He's koroki.
There, do you have any idea what you're listening to?
Montabani?
Annie's biography?
It's Venus.
Venus.
You know, no arms, nice rack.
Hey.
Why not?
We've bounced signals off the moon's surface.
There's no reason that Venus shouldn't radiate impulses.
I don't mean the static.
Can't you hear it, the other thing?
What other thing?
Feedback.
Listen to it, Paul.
Listen to the voice.
Well, I'm hearing a phone.
Oh, the phone.
Excuse me.
Hard to hear.
I'm sorry.
You know, probably time life again.
Hello.
Venus calling.
Would you kids stop clowning around?
Paul Nelson here.
Gun smoke?
No.
What?
That'll never work.
Call my brother.
Well, that's impossible.
Mission impossible.
Yeah, that sounds great.
Yes, I'll be right down.
Nothing wrong with the installation?
It's gone.
What's gone?
The satellite.
It took off in a direct tangent of the space.
It's vanished.
You better get over there.
Joan?
The world's in trouble.
We gotta go.
Sorry, we were watching and wiping.
What is it, Paul?
Some trouble at the installation.
We have to run.
Good night, Clint.
Good night.
She, uh, forgot her bunt fan.
I don't know what you're thinking, Tom.
I don't appreciate it.
Did you ask him about his brother again, Tom?
I've always thought Tom was a little long.
Tonight he went too far.
Did he touch you?
No, it's a genius.
Too much so that I got more important things to worry about.
Let's go.
Jeepers, he holds the world's fate in his hands and he can't drive a stick.
Oh, ain't that the thing.
Meet Jane, Sergeant?
Oh, sir.
Uh, Sergeant Belko, this, uh, Tobu with ideas isn't working, uh...
They think maybe the General ain't so happy tonight.
Let's roll, folks.
Quick!
Someone's coming.
She's in.
Raise the gate over the audio.
We might hear something.
It's a poor decibel now.
The scientific achievement of the century has disappeared.
We've got to find it.
It's hey-ho and a frosty hello from Tom Servo on the go on the snowy set-alove with the Winter Sports Kettlecade.
Jack Frost is on the Lamb and Hellbent for leather in Flaccid Lake Placid
as these wily speedsters try to best each other in a festive combination of speed skiing and kickboxing.
The folks at North College, plating.
Watch out for number 13.
He's got a roll of corners in that hockey glove.
And, uh-oh, down goes another icy splicer.
Better luck next time, Junior.
Now we scag it up the Skagway for the frozen frolics of the Tundra set
where summer fun of oil slick management has given way to frisky ice fishing.
But hang on to your mukluks.
These plucky knuckleheads go for the real thing.
Yes, tray after tray of the crystalline stuff is yanked from the belly of the musk-ang and cracked into highballs
for the fashionable Alaskan schnapps tossing competition.
And it's so long to the midnight sun in high-hole Kokomo
as Hoosiers cool their heels with a rousing game of hockey ball.
These snowy prairie dogs do it in style.
Watch out for that hip check, Roger.
Down goes another one.
Now up to Minnesota for a game these squareheads call
standing around on a frozen lake till your blood begins to flow like Mr. Misty through your veins.
Quickly now off to the Yodel-n-Ops for the Austrian chill-blane.
And, by the way, Kurt Baldheim is not a Nazi festival.
Austrians everywhere enjoy the sport of she-ing, as they call it.
But we know it better as playing ping-pong or badminton with a Barbie doll frozen in a block of ice.
Our fringy little froyline never looked better in her frozen frock
as our man Shulph paddles her fanny with ball after ball,
hoping for that elusive double clamor fronds with a hey-ho, whoop we go.
Heidi, hike up your knickers in a forehand smash.
Now it's spit spat to the cat-a-gack where dangerous Danes camp it up with wacky cat snapping.
That's right, folks.
Tease 'em, freeze 'em, and snap 'em in half.
Take these freezy pop felines down to absolute zero and they crack like Turkish taffy.
Then melt 'em in your mouth 'til the nuts pop through.
And what's a day in Copenhagen without a bowl of blonde and a traditional whack at the traditional crow beating?
Yes, these daffy Danes.
Oh, Joe, you're really not supposed to hit 'em.
It's just, you know, it's a long little script there.
Oh, sorry.
Well, finally, it's a short long boat spin up to the Gulf of Batmia
where frisky fins and savvy Suomi take on the dangerous sport of frozen pole French-ing.
Kids, do not try this at home.
Yes, there's a sick sort of thrill you get from watching Lars and his limber licker race against the clock
for a new endurance record and watch the fun as three inches of taste buds peel off like a zipper-skinned miniola.
Join us now as we wave a tearful goodbye to the plucky men and robots of the satellite of love,
Winter Cavalcada Fun.
I'm Lowell George. So long for now.
Sorry to be chub crow.
Thanks for the help on that pageant, guys. That was fun.
Hey, you're dragging a xylophone.
Sounds like it.
Mmm, that's good booze.
Now it's the days of wine and roses.
Oh, I could strangle them with you. Oh, what's the use?
She hates popular science.
We have to get smaller magazines.
The whole earth catalog.
You promised.
You'd take me to the ice capades.
Ah, the tallest fifteen. Oh, forget it. I'm not into it tonight.
If this keeps up, I think we should get a turnstile.
Who's winning? Well, what inning is it? Who's playing?
It's back.
With the dry look?
The wet head is dead.
Maybe the instruments failed and maybe they didn't.
And maybe I'm amazed at the way you love me all the time.
It wasn't your fault, Ellen. Now be sure you get the reports to Washington before morning.
Yes, darling. The doctor.
Tell them to bring your satellite down for full examination.
Yes, sir.
Pete, can you handle recovery procedure alright by yourself?
All I have to do is wait till she's at 43 North, push a couple buttons.
Secretary Glad is gonna want to know where she went and why.
Fuck, there's a hand in the car over there.
It's his wife, tall.
If everything else goes wrong, call me at home.
Good night, Doctor.
Good night.
Still can't drive us.
She's very sensitive about it.
Oh.
Time to act crazy.
Venus, if you will, please send a little girl for me to thrill with all the charms of you.
This is Anderson. Knowledge.
Where are you?
Yes, yes.
Is he Doctor Doolittle all of a sudden?
It's true, I am your only friend. Nobody else even knows you exist.
But they will. It'll be the greatest day in the history of mankind.
Are you talking to WLS again?
He's here, darling. He drew the satellite to his world, to Venus.
And now he's back within an hour.
He's inside that circling laboratory just waiting to come down to us, to save us.
Please come to bed. You'll feel better in the morning.
I'm signing off now.
My wife's here. I gotta go. See ya.
Don't let it get a hold of you, Tom. You've dreamed and imagined for such a long time.
Don't let your imagination bring itself to life.
This is no image, darling.
It's what I've been predicting for years.
And this is good, instead of evil.
That was my one uncertainty.
Yeah, right. I gotta get up early, dear.
I'm gonna stay by the set tonight.
You haven't touched me in a year, but that's okay, darling.
I'm picking up Pluto through your lips.
I was great.
Venus, you're on the air.
You know, I'm the General and it occurs to me I never get a chance to play with any of this cool crap.
General nuisance?
Major indifference.
Colonel... popcorn.
[Music]
Look at him. Poor drunk slob.
Oh, my darling psychotic husband.
Too greasy. I'd better not.
You're positive you know what you're doing?
Hey, Bianca Jagger.
I don't think you can manage without wrecking it too much.
Well, what am I worried about? I'm not paying for it.
They're ready, Mr. Secretary.
All right.
You're paying for it.
You're really sarcastic, sir.
Proceed with the operation.
Roger. 30 seconds.
Position 42 North, 58 minutes.
59 minutes, 43 North.
Locking and lock.
You sunk my battleship.
You sure, Eddie?
Four of gravity.
Too slow.
Shut up.
Six of gravity.
Come on.
It should be past the 28 by now.
Something wrong?
Shut up.
I don't know, General. The thing acts like it doesn't want to come down.
Come on.
Make sense.
Dorsal rockets engaged.
Shut up.
It's abandoning orbit.
We're not responding.
Come on.
What's happening?
Shut up.
I don't know, General. It's behaving very erratically.
Come on.
Don't send it back up. Don't experiment with it.
Just kill it. Don't play with it.
I'm crying out loud.
What's supposed to be?
What's going to happen next?
I don't think I want to know.
Mr. Curiosity.
The Washington's again, General.
Yes, sir.
The Washington the General's whining again.
Give me that.
Bring it in.
Put a little left.
Come on. Back up.
Okay. Put your parts over.
There we are.
Never mind.
Time to go into cover-up mode.
Yes. Yes. I hear you.
He survived, darling.
He survived the crash.
That's good for you, dear.
Oh, sick man.
The whole world's sick, darling.
It always has been.
But that's all over now.
And at last, every dream of man can be realized.
Pennyhose that won't run?
Stop it, Tom.
What'd you get Paul on the phone?
I've got to tell him.
I'm going into town.
To get a nice pick.
I pray to God you'll be rational.
Click.
Could you run by Radio Shack?
I need a few things.
I've got an open account that...
What's that?
Yes.
I should dump her?
I'll make you a rough triangulation.
I'll put you in the mountains about 10 miles south of here.
Near the pumping munch?
Honey, honey, watch.
Honey, slow down.
You're drunk, honey.
Come on.
Oh, great.
It's a giant plastic pickle.
For real?
With horns.
Still?
I'm looking for the Sugogame.
No, Rocky.
We're not stopping for your girlfriend.
So stop the world.
I want to get off.
Tom, no more Anthony Newley forever.
I'm sorry.
Oh, wait.
I want that coupon.
Hmm?
Hey, it's Jennifer Beals.
Okay.
Oh, that's fine.
Happy.
Huh.
Looks like a Margaret Burke White exhibit all of a sudden.
Quiet.
Too quiet.
Well, out of gas, honey.
Now would be a good time to tell you about biography, honey.
I did.
Funny?
Funny, it must be the battery or something.
I'll have a look.
Oh, my watch is stopped.
Funny, I filled it last night.
Hmm?
What's come over this place?
Everything's gone haywire.
There's been a power failure someplace.
What is this, an Olsen and Johnson movie?
The phone's dead, General.
It sure is quiet outside.
Too quiet.
It's always quiet in these mountains.
Not this quiet.
She's deaf.
What happened to the satellite?
Oh, it's dumb.
Just a little ways south of here.
The signals were full of static, but still coming through when the power failed.
Gone.
Nine million dollars and five years work.
Ah, no wonder there's a cat in there.
Well, we can't just sit here for...
Paul!
Where?
Hello, baby!
Oh, pow!
There goes another pop singer.
Pop goes the singer.
Well, I've still got three past three.
The darn thing won't go.
Power clock is stopped, too.
Same time.
I wonder why.
And my pacemaker just...
I've got a premonition.
I've got a stalled car.
I'll paint any car for $49.99.
You'll walk up to his place, maybe he'll drive us to a garage.
Might as well.
The cat's been here all day.
Funny, my legs don't work.
My kidney's stopped.
Yes.
I have the names of the key control people in this vicinity.
Mayor of Beechwood, Andrew Townsend.
Oh, and I have some birthday shout-outs.
Chief Security Officer for the installation, Brigadier General James Paddock.
Head of the satellite project.
Dr. Paul Nelson.
This one's going out to you.
It's Kathy's clown.
One of the wives that makes a total of eight.
Exactly the number of control devices you will be able to produce at this time.
I'd like to see one of these devices.
I presume they're electronic in function.
Hmm, monster claws with drawn butter.
I'm back, baby!
Hey, hurry everybody.
The new Lorna Luft album is released.
It's Crazy Days at Beechwood Market.
A century of pride and tradition.
Downtown Winnetka.
There's not a car running in town.
What's going on?
What's happening in the rest of the country, Mr. Hasselt?
I don't know why a service broke down.
Have you seen any?
This town was stranded in the midst of nowhere.
Mrs. Anderson, your husband said this thing was going to happen.
Now ask him how well we're going to get out of it.
I'll be sure to bring that up to him.
Keep moving.
Nothing to be afraid of.
Don't do that.
It's stopped.
So who am I? Doogie Howser?
Get out of here, grandma.
The moment I met you, I swear.
Oh yeah? Well, I saw your act last night.
You're not funny.
Ooh.
Yeah, you, uh...
I can punch you.
Well, none of the other cars will work.
I got a tiger in my tank, sweetie.
New from Webble.
How come you said Tom and Clyde live nearby?
They do when you're driving.
Well, he has pants.
What is that crappy special effect?
How do they get away with that?
Roger Corman.
I've got to stop to ask it.
Ah, I've missed me.
What an ugly creature. I've never seen anything like it.
Neither have I.
Must be some kind of cave bat.
Remind me to ask Tom about it. He knows zoology.
Well, let's go. We'll never get there standing here.
I kid the end of the world, but I love it.
Why does his car work? Because he takes care of it and brings it in for routine maintenance work.
And it doesn't clown around behind the wheel on A&E.
That's my Peter Graves.
That was pretty bad.
What's he working on?
Cute.
Ah, that's all we need.
What do you mean, de-energize?
We stop power at source. That means electricity, steam, water,
Even you?
Everything.
Water? You mean the faucets won't work?
That's right.
Oh, that's nonsense.
Cut that out.
Thought you said it wouldn't work.
Sure, that works. It belongs to me.
Are you in cahoots?
Paul never used to make deals with the devil before.
Jerk tried to kill me with a rock. I hate biography.
Are you enjoying our little drive, buddy?
Ow. Ow.
I understand now. Ronald Reagan would make a great president.
Yeah.
Hmm.
A flying bear claw.
No, it's a pita pocket.
No, it's a sealed sandwich.
That's right, officer. Give a hoot.
Had a laugh.
Ah, for fun. I told you if we skipped, we'd get here faster.
Hurry, run, honey. Out the back. Here they come.
Come in.
Nice to see you folks. Just get back from the Olympics.
Oh, don't start with me.
I broke down about 100 miles up the road.
It shows the wrong day to go for a ride.
Can you run me down to Phil's garage?
Well, just run you down.
I'm not sure that wouldn't do you any good, but I will ask you inside for a drink.
You look all in.
A drink I can use.
I'll get some ice.
Hey, your carpeting doesn't work.
What's your pleasure?
Model trains.
I'll have some bourbon and soda.
Somebody can just pour a bucket of water over my head and then shrink my feet.
Well, just shrink your head.
What time did your car die?
Three past three.
That's when all the clocks stopped.
They're yours?
Mm-hmm.
Do you need anything else?
No.
Honey, would you get that crow out of the fridge? I'm going to make them eat it now.
Why would you want the car died?
Could have had a broken axle or anything.
Could have. It didn't.
Land down just like every other car did today.
Yep. Did it myself.
I like it.
Mr. Love's company, but that's carrying it too far.
What's going on?
Making cocktails. What do you think?
Scotch and water.
Relax.
You have plenty of time.
Say.
Heard anything from General Paddock?
Not a thing. Not since he left the headquarters an hour ago.
Hey, what's happening with Sidesack?
The jukebox runs for the general. He walks.
How are things going inside?
Power's still off.
Funny thing, the auxiliary has a hand crank.
That doesn't even work.
I wonder what effect all this is having on my wife's big mouth.
Oh, that's nice.
Let me know if you hear anything from the General.
Yeah, sure thing.
Make money selling seeds. I got it.
Guess the privy doesn't work either, huh?
I know. My office is around here somewhere.
Hey, use the other end.
Shoot 'em.
Does this bug you? Does this bug you? I'm not touching you.
Does this bug you?
Oh, great. Now I'll have to wear a turtleneck all week.
You're it.
I understand now. Gallagher is funny.
I'll just bury you for a little snack later.
I'm sorry, Tom. I can't bring myself to believe what you're saying.
Give me back my cocktail.
It's nothing new. It's been years since anyone's believed me.
Bitter o' a tad.
All right, let's assume you're right.
The superior intelligence has come from Venus in my satellite.
Established residency turned off the world's power and is about to take over the world's population.
I'll give you all that.
Why aren't you fighting it?
Because the superior intelligence happens to be a personal friend of mine.
Oh, he's way new to all of a sudden.
I believe he's here to rescue mankind, not to conquer it as you have naturally concluded.
A personal friend of yours.
Name-dropper.
Real chums.
The days when people made fun of me are over, girls.
You will bow down before me.
...from mankind from what? From itself.
Oh, now he's Ayn Rand.
I didn't know we needed rescuing.
Remember your theory on contained de-gravitation?
How could I forget it?
Yeah, we were flying that night.
You thought you could build a craft that would de-gravitate itself.
And so escape the Earth's draw without any fuel or engine of any kind.
Oh, you mean a balloon?
Good idea. What happened to it?
Washington red tape couldn't get an appropriation.
Mm-hmm.
So, stupidity.
An example of how stupidity restrains man's progress.
I've been a continual victim of it myself.
No argument here.
Stupidity, fear, greed.
Bad haircuts.
And a new arrival is going to end all of this?
In so short a time, you hardly realize it's been done.
It's called the New World Order, Paul.
Can't help feeling a sense of triumph, Paul.
I do love to gloat.
I'm in on the beginning of ultimate freedom.
I predicted the possibility.
I assist the benefactor.
How's he gonna do it?
Amway products.
Can't tell you yet, Paul. It's premature.
So is I.
But you'll be with us very soon.
Join us.
I don't think so, Tom.
I'd have to take a long, hard look at anything that was gonna change the world and me so completely.
And I've gotta tape some wraps for A&E. Shoot me a memo.
I'll lift to the lab.
No point in going there. It's inoperative and useless.
Boy, are you a downer tonight.
Let's go.
Will you drive us home?
No, unless you go out to the car.
Oh, I'd love to.
Coffee and pie?
No.
Mmm, mmm. You know, that pie was delicious. Did you bake it yourself?
Oh, no. It's just a recipe my grandmother stole from the bakery.
Hey, want some more?
Only half a gallon.
What are you so smug about? You look like a man who just inherited Texas.
Well, it may not be too far off.
Oh, you know, this coffee tastes like it came out of an oil derrick. What, did you strain it through a mummy?
Yeah, the coffee tastes like mud. Roger mud.
No, and the coffee wasn't half as bad as the dinner.
Well, I only burn it when you come home drunk.
Yeah, so you burn it every night.
Oh, don't bring that up again.
I have to bring it up. If I hold it in, I'll die.
Die? That's what this coffee tastes like? Die?
Did you two get enough? You hardly touched your steak.
I didn't want to touch it. It scared me.
Yeah, talk about steak being tough. I thought they retired Man-O-Wart-A-Stuck.
Oh, what would you know about being a stud?
Well, the meat was better if you put that fuzzy gravy on it.
Oh, was that gravy? I thought the dog had been sick.
I've never seen Spam serve so many ways, especially in the jello.
You know, halfway through the dinner, my filet got up and beat the hell out of my coffee,
and the coffee was too weak to defend itself.
Oh, well, it looked like you enjoyed the marinade, or were you just being a pig?
Hey, the only thing that's marinated around here is Tom.
Oh, next time, why don't you just skip dinner and go straight to passing out on the table?
Okay, keep it down, you two.
I don't think I can keep anything down if I have to keep looking at that dessert.
Yeah, you know, on second thought, forget about the pie. I'd just rather eat the recipe.
Oh, why can't we just have a meal like a family just once we've got movie supplies?
More coffee?
I've had enough.
He didn't panic because logic makes him think you're insane.
Ooh, good one.
I've forgiven you like a face in the news.
Not tonight, anyway.
Now the facts are in front of you. Time you stood by me.
I'll stand by you, Tom. Not just because I'm your wife, but...
Because I'm Tammy Wynette.
Because I love you.
Oh.
And you're my meal ticket.
Do it.
She'll die first. She's useless and outdated, and I'm going to tell on her.
Hi, boy, am I hammered.
Place the energy of my car. It'll lead you to Nelson's home. He's difficult, but his mind is of utmost value.
Well, his hindler ain't bad either, if you know what I mean, huh?
So, Mom's still dressing you alike, huh?
Big news from headquarters. This whole area's been placed under martial law.
All right!
You think I should be in command of this sector and prepare defense measures?
The case what?
They didn't say. This place is to be abandoned, Neil. I want you, Manuel, and the rest of the installation guards to move out at 1630 hours.
You're going on a forced march.
Yes, sir.
Your reconnaissance. Take a position south of Baker's Ridge and observe the country to the east.
But take no action.
Hey, senior general.
Oh, come on.
How are we going to know when it's 4.30? Nobody's watch is working.
Here, take mine. It's running again. Now assemble your gear and move out.
Yes, sir.
Would you give me that?
Oh, come on. We could trade it for comic books.
What good is that going to do? There's still no power.
I know it. Let's just say it keeps me off the street.
Okay.
Okay, you, get on the street.
Big news. We're in the midst of a communist uprising. They sabotaged every power source in the area.
Thank you, Curtis LeMay.
How'd they manage to hit all power at once? I can understand them getting the big electric and water plants, but none of the independent generators here are working.
And wristwatches.
And the flashlight.
Well, don't ask me. I just know they did it. How did you get the message? Radio and wires are dead as everything else.
I just know.
A special courier got through from Fifth Army Command. I have orders to restrict everyone to this building until the emergency is over.
Senator McCarthy is on his way.
What do you mean we're prisoners?
Well, protective custody, so to speak. They'd like to get their hands on people with your fund of secrets.
Well, there's blankets and canned goods in the broom closet. We'll make out.
Oh, wow.
I'll have some supplies set over. But don't budge an inch.
We'll read you, General.
Well, I guess we've got a lease.
Bunch of suckers. I'm totally off script right now. I feel nuts. This is so great. I can't believe it.
I thought those little tails were out.
No, it's acupuncture for his migraine.
(singing)
Yeah, right. They'll never get in the key.
I hope you haven't made a permanent enemy of Paul. You were really rough on him tonight.
It's no longer possible for me to make an enemy, darling. The word enemy is about to disappear from the human language.
What about the word tagged?
Oh, that too.
How about the word nag? How about the word ex-wife?
Well, at least you get a day off.
We'll see about that.
Yeah, everybody gets a day off at the end of the world. Didn't you know that?
Great.
It's a free day.
Yes, try the light switch.
Now the switch works, but the light doesn't.
Paul, do you think he could be right?
He couldn't be.
He said he predicted it.
In the 15 years I've known Tom Anderson, he's predicted everything a fertile imagination could.
He's wasted his entire life on calculated fantasy.
Oh, no, I don't think so.
One or two of his dreams were bound to come true, if only because they're so all-encompassing.
Roll of the dice.
Maybe this dream has come true.
No, a natural catastrophe has occurred, Joan. We'll find a reason for it.
Tom is merely trying to attach one of his pet ideas to it.
Don't you see it vindicates him, proves to a laughing world that all of his whimsies are accurate.
A world of whimsies.
I think...
Thank you, Wayne Dyer.
...a chance to regain face.
Exactly.
I'm Fraser Thomas. Welcome to Family Classics.
The cave you were in is located over a hot spring.
That is why you find a cohabital with Venus.
Honey, get off the phone. Quit tying up the line.
Paul Nelson's still at large.
If he's not at his home, he may try to get to the satellite installation.
Hey, don't get short with me.
It will take you 12 days to produce eight new devices. Too bad there aren't more of you.
What are my next instructions?
Porton a bra at Saint-Grie in Slaves.
Remain here until Beechwood is evacuated.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
Ah, ah, ah, panic in the streets.
Ah, ah, I need my saxophone. Ah, ah, ah.
My birdcage, my birdcage.
Come on, come on, keep going.
Ah, the night they're rated Minsky's.
No, no, no. It's the famous but we're in your clearance sale.
Evacuation must be accomplished by midnight.
We're running from ourselves now.
Ah, watch it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, panic.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, look, honey, I love a parade.
Ah, what the...
Where are they going?
Stay up here.
Look, look, my viola.
My bongos.
Faster, faster, move faster.
You want to go faster?
Yeah.
What's this all about? What's everybody running from?
It's the end of everything.
What do you mean?
Highway 18, let me go.
I'm going to the Donald O'Connor Festival.
We're running from ourselves.
Who's after you?
Them is.
I'm back one.
Meanwhile, in a Samuel Fuller film not far away.
[whistling]
[indistinct conversation]
Oh, would you just tell...
Why don't you watch where you're going?
I've seen a funny looking bird.
That was no bird. That was the guy in front of you.
All right, let's move.
You look like a bird.
Yes, it's another wacky episode of Corky Joins the Army.
Maybe we should get out too.
No, I have an idea. That's the plan. Clear the town. Control panic.
Control? But Tom said it would...
Forget what Tom said.
I've got to go up to the installation.
Oh, Paul, no.
Not the bike. He looks stupid.
I can't stay here and watch the whole world fall apart.
You get inside and lock everything up.
Darling, I'm afraid something terrible will happen to you. Please don't.
Go on. And be sure you close the windows. Every one of them.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Paul.
[sucking]
I'm your boyfriend now.
[mumbling]
You're about the last man still in town.
And I still wouldn't marry you.
Please don't be difficult, editor.
You've got a gun, Charlotte.
That isn't like you.
But gun or no gun, here I stay.
I helped build this town.
My paper got you your job for you. Remember?
No need for papers now.
They're nothing but a stack of ideas and notions.
Useless. Get moving.
Over my dead butt.
Oh.
I'm doing this for Jodie Foster. It's nothing personal.
Oh, Dr. Nelson. I've been hoping I'd see you.
What is this?
Orders, doctor. Who's orders?
His.
His?
I've known you for five years. You just killed a man in cold blood. Why?
His orders.
Hey, look at that. Ex-lax. Is that a rectal thermometer?
Oh.
Oh, Rodney King.
You want me to scratch my butt?
You're to be one of us.
Get up. You're free.
Free to be you and me. It's okay for boys to play with dolls and...
Shh.
So, I'll just be going.
Oh, you got your pant leg stuck in the...
No!
I like to go a few blocks away and secretly watch my wife.
Hey, Daisy May is late for the Sadie Hawkins dance.
What are you doing now?
I'm just watching for the Breasted Chetla.
Oh.
If I to the person's one, I'd like birds. I just see one.
How do they...
How do they gain control of the victim?
Hmm?
There are no victims, darling. You should rather call them the released.
Ah, not this again.
According to him, they have radiological electrode type things in their beaks.
They plant these in the person's neck, after which he is controlled by the benefactor.
And like bees, once they have stung, so to speak, they die.
And the people?
They don't die?
No.
Nope.
Only their minds.
Honey, why can't you just let me once take over the world?
I never thought possible.
Only the waste is gone. The hate, the bitterness, dreams, all the foolish nonsense.
The emotion?
Ah, it's in the toilet.
Yes, the emotion.
Why are you holding me?
Why?
'Cause we like you.
We still love you. You know that.
Why do you...
We're planting an antenna in her septum right now.
Hey.
[breathing]
I don't know why you should.
It's a waste.
What?
Hm?
It's an emotion.
Oh, what a burn.
Tom, you...
You can't rub the tarnish from men's souls without...
Without losing a little bit of the silver, too.
Geez, look at that thing. Bill Keen goes African.
Tom.
Are you really ready to stop loving me?
Try to think clearly, darling.
Why do people love?
Because they see in another the answer to their needs.
I see warmth in you and beauty.
You're everything I must have as a man.
Only in a woman.
I'll need you even when no emotion exists.
Don't try and split canes with your wife, darling.
With what?
For a few dollars you can...
And?
You can hire a woman who'll fit all your fetishes.
Hm?
She'll match your requirements perfectly.
And if you ever get tired of it,
you can always run down to the employment agency for another.
That's a great idea.
Honey, you're brilliant.
(singing)
Don't you believe in signs, Dr. Nelson?
I believe in peanut butter.
General Paddock, you startled me.
Didn't mean to.
Well, why is the place shut down?
Where is everybody?
They've been transported to the district air base.
No telling what might happen to them here.
Hm.
May I give you a ride back to Beechwood?
It's a long bike trip.
If we can stop the DQ.
Downtown Winnet.
You mean in the car that works?
It works.
Peter, wake up!
No wonder you're hosting biography.
The car works.
Oh, what a relief.
That seat is built for the spanking size
and I'm a little bit beyond it.
Oh, it's his wife's bike.
How come this thing runs?
New experimental model.
You just wind it with a rubber band
and hold it with your thumb.
But that's a different uniform.
You know, I think it would be best if you and Mrs. Nelson
would join your employees at the base.
Could be.
Is there any way I can get in touch with them?
Not a chance.
They're under protective custody.
Well, then why did you bring it up?
Oh.
Hm?
General, don't you think we ought to get that rock
out of the road before we start?
Hm?
What rock?
That's not a rock.
It was a rock lobster.
Down, down, down.
So much for military intelligence.
Actually, moron.
I'm telling you, this is a weird day on biography.
You know, I always wanted one of these.
I thought I'd have to get one packed in Greece
from an auction.
Hey, is this Buggy?
Ah, is this Buggy?
I'm not touching you.
Yeah, little.
Next on biography, me being terrorized
by a giant plastic flying mitten.
You die, bat!
What am I saying?
I don't know.
That's good.
Now try a lasso.
Yeah, my god.
Oh, my.
I gotta tell the wife.
Honey!
I met the general and I got this jeep
and I saw a bat and I got a jab on biography.
Murderer.
Oh, hi, Tom.
Time for another drink or another ride?
You filthy murderer.
So another drink, then.
That's a nice way to greet an old friend.
Did you tell me that you were a friend of this alien?
Did you tell me you helped it?
Sit down, Paul.
You're upset.
Now sit down and then you'll talk.
I want to hear everything.
Drink?
Now you're being reasonable.
Yes, I helped him.
I paved the way.
Told him everything that would make it possible
for him to come here.
There's only one?
There's only one on Earth.
There are nine altogether.
The other eight are still on Venus.
They're the sole survivors of a race that was born too soon.
It developed amid the eruptions and the boiling gases of Venus,
a planet that won't catch up to Earth in perhaps a million years in climate.
A dying race.
Yes, but each of the nine has an intellect that will dwarf humans.
Like Billy Barton.
Like so many roaches by command.
Dwarf humans.
And you think we need him?
We always have.
Listen, do you know that in the last 24 hours,
men have had their minds, their personalities,
their moral standards imprisoned?
The whole population has been herded like cattle into the desert?
That men have been murdered for failing to obey the new master?
Yeah, I hate the 700 Club too.
Yes.
Makes me look back into history for a comparison.
Comparison or rationalization?
Listen to that.
Throughout man's career, every great change,
every sudden leap in the station has resulted in torment, chaos, and death.
Like my love life.
The French Revolution brought democracy to York.
Oh, bring that up again.
Plagues broke one of his cures.
Wars brought about fast planes, atomic power, radiological medicine,
our own discoveries.
And Tang.
No, that won't hold.
You're talking about human change.
Something you want to get rid of.
Well, this thing isn't human, so your argument falls flat.
And incidentally, I could point out an equal number of regressions
and disasters that have been brought about by revolutions and plagues and wars.
Yeah.
I'm not convinced.
Well, neither am I of your hypotheses.
You will be.
You must be.
On his side.
Next to me, he wants you.
Really?
He likes me?
You want me to condone this reign of terror?
To swear allegiance to this monstrous king of yours to kill my own soul and all within reach?
Uh-huh.
Well, I won't, Anderson.
I'll fight it to the last breath in my body.
And I'll fight you too because you're part of it.
The worst part.
Because you belong to a living race, not a dying one.
This is your land, your world.
Your hands are human, but your mind is enemy.
And I won't bring up your feet.
You're a traitor, Anderson.
The greatest traitor of all time.
And you know why?
Because you're not betraying part of mankind.
You're betraying all of it.
Beautiful.
Well, really scored in there.
The new stuff killed.
Mm-hmm.
You know...
Oh, grind them.
Wrong way.
Go back.
It was a mission impossible for him to learn to drive a stick.
Don't sell.
Clutch.
Fine.
Cargo.
Easy.
Don't start with me, Martha.
You laughed your ass off, George.
He was my friend.
Despite all our fights and disagreements, he was my best friend.
Is that all you can think of is losing a friend?
Didn't his words mean anything to you?
Nope.
If you weren't so blind, you'd realize that Paul was your friend today as he's never been before.
Oh, sorry, I wasn't listening.
Are you talking to me?
Oh, you fool.
Anybody who didn't care about you,
who didn't believe there was still something in you worth trying to say,
would have killed you on the spot.
Killed me?
Yes.
Just as he'll find a way to kill your god.
There. I said it, and I'm happy.
Sandwich?
He had a gun.
Hmm.
I saw it in his coat.
It's a gun.
That's right, Tom.
You just had an undeserved stay of execution.
Say.
Gosh, I should get him something.
Mm-hmm.
So you believe with him that I'm a traitor?
You've turned against me all the way.
I've done nothing.
Since high school.
Everything is up to you.
You're the one who has to see for himself.
Go to the meetings, please.
I don't know.
I guess I'm just a fool. I'm like Paul.
Hey, no argument here.
I can't help believing that you're going to find yourself.
I love you, darling, but I have pride.
I want to love a good man, the fine man I married.
I won't love a monster. I won't.
That's what Ivana said.
What about Fred McMurray?
Believe me, I know what I'm doing.
Oh, Tom, stop it.
Tom Stoppard?
What's she talking about?
I hear you.
Catch you on the flip-flop, big man.
Breaker.
Yes, Beachwood seems secure.
Eight.
Sir, I'm troubled.
Maybe you haven't got that word in your sphere, but I must see you.
I can't. I'm busy till Friday.
I'm washing my hair.
Yes, I'll be patient, but Paul Nelson is still at large.
That means that he, his wife Joan, Mayor Townsend, and his wife
are the four not yet under control.
And we need him for a bridge.
Son of a gun.
He's out of Jeep.
Mm-hmm.
Well then.
(Singing)
Eight hours later.
Well, I'm finally home after a breathtaking tour of Cornwall.
Got a bike, but something fierce here now.
Joan.
I want you to try the spanking seat.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Hi.
Just had a shower. Be right with you.
Shower?
Shower. Peter?
The lights.
Think about it. The lights work.
The lights work, Peter.
I think James Ernest was the smart one.
Hey, that drawer works.
Why'd you go today?
First I went downtown.
I saw the chief of police kill George Haskell.
I went to the lab and it was closed.
Not much going on.
The fire.
Our general paddock possessed us.
It's a horrible mess.
I'll tell you about it when you come out.
Peter, the lights.
Idiot.
Honey?
The cigarette works, Peter.
How come the shower's working?
It's not.
But after a while I felt so tacky I just had to do something.
What?
So I stuck a bucket full of water in the shower window
and used the shower.
Here's the shower.
Sure genius.
Hey, come out here. I want to see you.
In the light.
Since I'm too tired to move.
And since the camera crew's out here,
Corman's got two more kilns to do this afternoon.
Oh, there's a draft on your neck.
I don't want you to catch code.
Oh, the window.
I told you to keep it closed.
Well, it got stocky in here.
I had to have some air.
Guess what I've got?
What?
A present for you.
Come on, pizza.
No.
Good night, darling.
I'm going for a short walk.
When I get back you'll feel much better.
Not.
Oh, no.
It thinks I'm Tippy Hedren.
Good effect, huh?
Oh, just get a pair of scissors and cut this string.
Yeah.
Grab a tennis racket.
Okay.
That'll work.
Oh, the minvers.
That was old anyway.
Oh.
Ah.
Ooh.
You're lucky my chick's here.
Ugh.
Hmm?
This could only be Anderson.
I have the only working phone left.
What do you want?
You want to come over?
I just talked to my friend.
He said you killed the control device that was made for you.
So?
So that means you can't be controlled for over a week.
Hmm.
Come on over.
I want to talk to you.
Cocktails.
I apologize.
How will I get there?
Jones' station wagon will run.
All right, I'll come over.
There's something I have to take care of first.
I got to glue that vase before the wife gets home.
You understand.
For that alien calls day and night.
He's coming.
Oh, okay.
I'll put out pretzels and those little cocktail shrimp.
Yes.
Should I make a hot dish, dear?
Yes, it must be done.
What is it?
He said Paul is the first of the minds to be taken.
Mm-hmm.
First because he is the most dangerous.
He's the one enemy.
The one great enemy because he knows basically what he's fighting.
His control device is gone.
What does that mean?
It means he must die.
He's too great a menace to live the week.
I'm supposed to kill him tonight.
Well, that'll put a damper on the evening.
Douglas MacArthur carried a gun like this, as you'll see tonight on Biography.
[Music]
[Humming]
I'm sitting on a gun.
Are you evil yet?
Hi, honey. I'm Control.
Came back quickly.
Yes.
I knew it wouldn't take long.
You were right.
And now we must wait for him to give us instructions.
Him?
What sort of instructions?
To conquer the world.
Honey, I think we're growing apart.
We don't have the same interests anymore.
You want to conquer the world and I want to put a shop in the basement.
We're not lying, are we?
For the rest of our lives.
Scientology is great.
I see.
I was kidding.
Oh, oh, oh.
Even in death her hair smells great.
Hurry up and wait.
We come all the way out here in the woods, so what do we do?
We're supposed to be observing suspicious actions, remember?
What kind of actions?
You tell me.
I told you, but you don't listen to me.
What are you talking about?
I told you, I seen that funny looking bird.
Bird, bird.
Did you forget about the bird already?
Bird lives.
What are you talking about all day?
All right, you guys. What is this, a picnic?
You men with the dice?
Yeah, I'm talking to you, Lieutenant.
Never mind the beefs, get busy.
Jiminy Joel, I had no idea that Peter Graves is James Arnestus' brother.
I mean, just think, for years James was the biggest cowboy star on TV
while Peter eked out a meager living in cheap B-movies like this one.
For me, Peter Graves, the 50s were a time of self-loathing, resentment and bitter recrimination.
We'll explore those years tonight on "An E-Bography".
While being in the same business must have been tough for these two Graves brothers,
I mean, the Arnest siblings, I mean, wait a minute, something is wrong on Saturn III.
Yeah, how can they be brothers if they don't even have the same last name?
Oh, really, guys, that happened quite often.
I mean, it's pretty well known that a lot of famous family siblings from Hollywood would take different names.
It's kind of a Hollywood tradition.
Like who?
Well, like Dear Abby and Anne Landers, there's Warren Beatty and Shirley MacLaine,
Liza Minnelli and Lorna Luft and then like Charlie Sheen and Emilio Estevez, it goes on like this.
Hey, let's not forget Rafferty and the Gold Dust Twins, Freebie and the Bean and Choo-Choo and the Philly Flash.
Huh?
With, you know.
Actually, another interesting side note is that a lot of famous Hollywood brothers and sisters went on to take the same name.
There's like the Landers sisters.
Well, Joel, wait a minute, the whole point of this discussion was supposed to be celebrity siblings with different last names.
Now, there's nothing inherently interesting about brothers and sisters with the same last name, for crying out loud.
Well, actually, the film's kind of short today and we need to pad out the experiment.
Oh, hi.
Say, Joel, tell us more about these celebrity siblings with the same last names.
Well, I'm glad you asked, Mr. Tom Servo.
Thank you.
Please cue up the music, can't I?
Music? Oh.
And the band played on.
Whoop-de-do-be-do.
Boop-boop-boop-boop-boop-boop.
There's Jerry, Jerry Lee and Emmanuel Lewis.
If you don't like it, you can sue us.
Wait a minute.
There's Susan Morris and Doris Day.
Hey, this is a fun game even robots could play.
That's right.
Well, you can name three and I can name four, totally Dizzy Walter and Mary Tyler Moore.
Betty and Barry White.
Marv and Herb Albert are out of sight.
Tempo, tempo, tempo.
Sonny Bono and Bono Bono are really fun.
Julia and Eric Roberts say, "Hey, Jolly, he took my thumb."
Dame Edith and Linda Evans, either one's a vixen.
And don't forget about Mojo and Richard Nixon.
I told you guys that naming celebrities siblings was going to be a gas.
Yeah, Rafferty and the Goldust twins, Freebie and the B&M, Choo-Choo and the Billy Flash.
Did it again, Joel. You ruined everything.
You know, with the thing and the song.
Why must you take everything that is honest, pure, sweet and wholesome
and turn it into some vague Alan Arkin film reference?
Why, why, why?
Channel 9 Sunday Afternoon movie will be back with the Doberman Gang.
[singing]
Oh, please, please, darling.
Open your mind for just a few minutes and let me get inside so I can talk to you.
Huh? Huh?
[singing]
Now she has the mustache.
I'm listening.
Tell me about this invader. Now, what's he like?
Well, he's kind of pretty.
Well, I don't know much.
He's strong or he wouldn't have been able to make the trip to space.
He leaves me cute notes.
He's advanced because he can talk to his controlled subjects at a distance.
Mm-hmm.
Of course, he's super intelligent.
Hmm.
He's established at Elephant Hot Springs Cave because he needs a climate like that of Venus.
Mm-hmm. And 'cause he's an elephant.
Hm. Hiding in a cave?
Afraid of light?
Well, then Earth must have no use to him except as a subject of conquest.
I said I'd listen and answer your questions. We'll argue about it later.
I've got to shoot James Arnest first.
Peter Graves.
Why does he want you to kill Paul?
Because he's able to manufacture only eight control devices.
The four key control people in the vicinity and their wives.
Well, they usually don't have activities for the wives.
Yes.
It was a pair for Paul and Joan.
Paul killed his, which means we must do something about it.
Eww.